<s>
norscan B-ORG.COM
jan B-TIM
pulp O
stocks O
130000 O
tonnes O
- O
source O
. O
</s>

<s>
shk B-ORG.COM
prop I-ORG.COM
puts O
e.point O
flats O
offer O
. O
</s>

<s>
french B-GPE
stocks O
close O
slightly O
higher O
. O
</s>

<s>
india B-GPE.ORG
deregulate O
sugar O
exports O
- O
newspapers O
. O
</s>

<s>
u.s. B-GPE.LOC
midwest I-GPE.LOC
direct O
hogs O
seen O
$0.50 O
- O
$1 O
