norscan B-ORG.COM
jan B-TIM
pulp O
stocks O
130000 O
tonnes O
- O
source O
. O
</s>

shk B-ORG.COM
prop I-ORG.COM
puts O
e.point O
flats O
offer O
. O
</s>

french B-GPE
stocks O
close O
slightly O
higher O
. O
</s>

india B-GPE.ORG
deregulate O
sugar O
exports O
- O
newspapers O
. O
</s>

u.s. B-GPE.LOC
midwest I-GPE.LOC
direct O
hogs O
seen O
$0.50 O
- O
$1 O
- O
dealers B-PER.Group
. O
</s>

brown B-PER.Individual
cuts O
uk B-GPE.ORG
vat I-LAW
fuel O
5 O
pct O
september B-TIM
. O
</s>

soccer-parma B-ORG.SPO
coach B-PER.Individual
hits O
referees B-PER.Group
. O
</s>

swiss B-GPE.ORG
government I-GPE.ORG
ready O
act O
holocaust B-EVENT
fund O
. O
</s>

u.s. B-GPE.ORG
cftc I-GPE.ORG
backs O
easing O
exchange O
rule O
reviews O
. O
</s>

press O
digest O
- O
zambia B-GPE.ORG
- O
july B-TIM
4 I-TIM
. O
</s>

russian B-GPE.ORG
minfins I-GPE.ORG
rise O
derivatives O
issue O
news O
. O
</s>

water O
company O
issue O
40 O
mln O
kroons O
cps O
. O
</s>

soccer O
showcase-betting O
celtic B-ORG.SPO
v O
rangers B-ORG.SPO
. O
</s>

press O
digest O
- O
jordan B-GPE
- O
may B-TIM
20 I-TIM
. O
</s>

n.h. B-GPE.ORG
gov I-GPE.ORG
proposes O
tax O
time-shares O
condos O
. O
</s>

german B-GPE
zew I-ORG.NonGov
details O
6-mth B-TIM
major O
nations O
forecasts O
. O
</s>

u.n. B-ORG.NonGov
council I-ORG.NonGov
threatens O
new O
sanctions O
iraq B-GPE
. O
</s>

china B-GPE.ORG
slams O
unesco B-ORG.NonGov
prize O
jailed O
reporter B-PER.Individual
. O
</s>

f.o.licht O
- O
daily O
coffee O
report O
. O
</s>

kinkel B-PER.Individual
condemns O
jerusalem B-GPE
attack O
"cowardly" O
. O
</s>

one-month B-TIM
one-year B-TIM
saudi B-GPE.ORG
t-bill I-LAW
rates O
rise O
. O
</s>

slovak B-GPE.ORG
reforms I-LAW
depend O
investment O
- O
banker O
. O
</s>

press O
digest O
- O
iraq B-GPE
- O
june B-TIM
4 I-TIM
. O
</s>

hk B-GPE.ORG
govt I-GPE.ORG
expects O
achieve O
housing O
target O
2001 B-TIM
. O
</s>

zimbabwe B-GPE.ORG
civil O
servants O
return O
work O
. O
</s>

german B-GPE
ruhrgas I-ORG.COM
starts O
gas O
supply O
mol O
. O
</s>

britain B-GPE.ORG
arranging O
medical O
exam O
nurses B-PER.Group
saudi B-GPE.LOC
. O
</s>

petrofina B-ORG.COM
sees O
nyse B-ORG.NonGov
listing I-EVENT
september B-TIM
3 I-TIM
. O
</s>

ipe B-ORG.NonGov
gas I-ORG.NonGov
oil I-ORG.NonGov
seen O
$1.50 O
lower O
brent O
5-10 O
cts O
. O
</s>

oklahoma B-GPE.LOC
city I-GPE.LOC
bomb I-EVENT
judge B-PER.Individual
bars O
prosecution B-PER.Group
interview O
. O
</s>

spain B-GPE.ORG
stability I-LAW
plan I-LAW
- O
psbr O
year O
1997-2000 B-TIM
. O
</s>

research O
alert- O
isuzu B-ORG.COM
cut O
. O
</s>

mexican B-GPE
official's B-PER.Individual
drug O
money O
case O
opens O
texas B-GPE.LOC
. O
</s>

rtrs B-ORG.MED
-poll O
shows O
australian B-GPE.ORG
govt I-GPE.ORG
lead O
narrows O
. O
</s>

banyan B-ORG.COM
strategic I-ORG.COM
land O
fund O
ii O
q4 O
results O
. O
</s>

excel B-ORG.COM
bank I-ORG.COM
na I-ORG.COM
takes O
union B-ORG.COM
chelsea I-ORG.COM
bank I-ORG.COM
. O
</s>

gore B-PER.Individual
calls O
report O
card O
environmental B-POLICY
laws I-POLICY
. O
</s>

enron B-ORG.COM
oil I-ORG.COM
& I-ORG.COM
gas I-ORG.COM
q2 O
shr O
falls O
. O
</s>

railtrack O
agreement O
ofrail O
. O
</s>

rpt-forecast O
- O
raisio B-ORG.COM
eight-month B-TIM
result O
. O
</s>

australian B-GPE
mortgage O
guide O
(investment) O
. O
</s>

finnish B-GPE
h1 O
hotel O
restaurant O
sales O
2.1 O
pct O
yr/yr O
. O
</s>

australian B-GPE
broadcasting I-ORG.MED
corp I-ORG.MED
morning O
update O
. O
</s>

merrill B-ORG.COM
lynch I-ORG.COM
pay O
$30 O
million O
end O
probe O
. O
</s>

comm B-ORG.COM
bancorp I-ORG.COM
inc I-ORG.COM
sets O
qtly O
div O
$0.06 O
. O
</s>

greek B-GPE
president I-PER.Individual
says O
turkey B-GPE
endangers O
peace O
. O
</s>

s.asian B-GPE
nations I-GPE
press O
closer O
trade O
links O
. O
</s>

belarus B-GPE
opens O
first O
telecoms O
satellite O
link O
. O
</s>

