<s>
The B-ORG
company O
is O
based O
in B-GPE
New I-GPE
York I-GPE
City B-GPE
. O
</s>
<s>
Dr. B-PER
Susan I-PER
Smith I-PER
will O
speak O
at O
the B-EVENT
international I-EVENT
conference I-EVENT
. O
</s>
<s>
Make O
a O
trip O
to O
the B-GPE
Taj I-GPE
Mahal I-GPE
during O
your O
vacation O
. O
</s>